NewTube.
Every minute, it sees hundreds
of hours of video uploaded,
as well as hundreds of thousands
of hours of video watched,
making it the world's most-visited website.
Katsudon: It's almost time
ohashi: gg masakichi
Hibiscus: Are you two okay?
Don't push yourselves
Chachamaru: Hellooo
nemo: hey
kkkk0302: yo losers
imhungry: Masakichi's done for!
Masakichi's done for!
Ishibashi T. Wataru: Man up and step down
Gakkey: What happened?
Sparkling * Chondroitin: kikka a cute
Lonely Oedo Girl: Think about how the fans feel.
How about I punch you too??
lol lmao: apology stream yessssss
Vitamin B2: Unforgivable
Kai10: Are you two okay...?
These comments, I swear...
Hype-Sis
Urgent Announcement
Utter trash.
What do they know?!
To all of you who continue to
support us, thank you so much.
Today, we have an announcement to make.
First, regarding the past several videos,
we would like to apologize for
any discomfort they may have caused.
To set things right, we've decided
to let Masakichi go as a member.
She's been making videos with us
since high school,
so we wanted to keep her on if possible,
Breaking: Masakichi fired
Fifth Champion Tanaka: The latest videos were awful.
Are you two okay?
It's me, Hana: Masakichi's out, huh? Makes sense
Avocado: No one likes Masakichi anyway, so who cares?
pui: lol fired lmao
Black-Hearted Kurosuke: The videos were hard to watch.
I sincerely hope this leads to the best for all three of you.
Antinomy: Masakichi ruins the videos. I hate seeing her.
smooth finish: show her face already
but the truth is that we haven't been
on good terms for some time now.
From frustration about not getting views,
to complaints about the content of our videos
and differences in enthusiasm levels...
We had our fair share of arguments,
followed by her violent outburst
the other day during our livestream...
So what?
It's all my fault now?
...and the toxic posts
discovered on her alt after that.
stinger @chikchik_m3k
She wasn't the one I punched, so what's her deal?
Stop playing the victim... So annoying
stinger @chikchik_m3k
You seriously can't even do this? So useless
God they're so needy
We want everyone to enjoy watching
the Hyped-Up Sisters channel,
so we can't overlook these actions
from one of our members.
Screw you!
Re: She crossed the line there
JO: true lol
I quit: Bye masakichi
Yasu: Yeah figures
apple: so long
Wrinkled dress shirt: well duh
jiji: Right move
Lonely Oedo Girl: Eat ittttttttttttttt
human: violent bitch die die die die die
edamame: i hope you never change otomin
ky: Cut it out already
Iburi Gakko Enthusiast: I know it won't be easy
going forward, but I'm rooting for you!
gun666: Show yourself, Masakichi
Eye Drops: Go away loser
bom777: ggwp
Ma: Why are you two apologizing?
tasteless odorless: You might be better off
going your separate ways.
No way...
After getting together as a group to
discuss these incidents and our next steps,
The haters are the ones to blame here!
I did nothing wrong!
the two of us and Masakichi
have decided to go our separate ways.
If all of you watching
can find it to forgive us,
What?!
we would like to continue Hype-Sis with
just the two of us, Otomin and Kicchomu.
You're the ones who made that decision for me!
We would like to take this
opportunity to make a fresh start,
and focus on diligently making videos
that all of our viewers can enjoy.
As the new and reborn Hyped-Up Sisters,
we'll do our best to hit the goal Masakichi had set
of reaching one million channel subscribers.
Finally, please continue to support us—
The Canceled Girl and the Sleepy Vampire
One Moment, Please
Now you've made another mess.
That's a lot of comments.
Man, looks like you racked up a ton of hits.
All thanks to you.
You're welcome.
Also, a million subs?
No way!
No one will stick around once I'm gone.
We won't let them slip away.
We'll keep growing our numbers.
But I'm the one who came up
with all our video ideas!
You just wanted to call all the shots.
I was the one who filmed and edited—
We'll do what we can!
Besides, it'll be smooth sailing
if we hire someone new!
We're going to start the stream again.
Will you join us?
Well, not like anyone wants
to see a violent bitch like you.
No way!
Hey, there! Masakichi here!
I've decided to start a solo channel!
This channel will be for videos of
all the things I really wanted to do!
The comments are a war zone!
Yes, yes!
tommy: Have you ever considered how
the two Hype-Sis members must feel?
Shushusuke: I had to stop watching after the first minute
Tangerine Jelly: Please don't upload any more videos
yamamomo: Are you really taking this attitude
after punching someone? You can't just pretend it
didn't happen, so please apologize to the other two
and give us fans a proper explanation.
merorin: why the hell would you start a solo channel
Milk Tea: All she thinks about is herself.
She doesn't care at all how the fans feel.
SE: A 10 min video yapping about herself
and zero apologies lmao
otooto: The stuff about recent gripes is w/e,
but I can't forgive you for punching Otomin.
I'll get everyone talking
and blow those two out of the water!
All the ideas that wouldn't have
flown before are fair game now!
Rice: she doesn't regret anything she did
aa: So this is what Masakichi is really like..
tomtom: Seriously messed up as a person
Shrimp: Think about the other two a little
amebaaaaaaaa: Nice sockpuppet
sdsjkfha: Please. Just quit already.
The Great Acorn: Turns out Masakichi's
willing to do whatever it takes
for her own success.
Please support the channel,
like, and subscribe!
This is your chance to witness a legend!
What, really?
Not even one positive comment?
This isn't good!
Damage control, damage control!
Masakichi-san, I'm a huge fan of yours!
"Masakichi-san, I'm a huge fan of yours!"
"You have my support!"
Masakichi-san, I'm a huge fan of yours!
Daifuku Mochi: Who are you going to punch next??
Seltzer Water: Don't be so full of yourself.
You're not even cute.
AT: Support? That's gotta be her posting lol
hypehype: Masakichi-san, I'm a huge fan of yours!
You have my support!
tommy: Have you ever considered how the
two Hype-Sis members must feel?
Shushusuke: I had to stop watching after the first minute
No more!
I'm not looking!
Say what you want!
nanamichan: I haven't seen all of Hype-Sis's videos,
but I can't support Masakichi-san anymore.
rice on rice: What's with the heel turn?
Hojicha Ice Cream: She's got a talent for offending people
MIU: So much for thinking that Masakichi was a cute,
funny girl with a good personality.
chopsticks: Was starting a solo channel
really your highest priority here?
She's got a talent for offending people
So much for thinking that Masakichi was a cute, funny girl
with a good personality.
Was starting a solo channel really your highest priority here?
Yeah, maybe I should have started
with an apology video.
Sorry
There.
Not like anyone wants to see
a violent bitch like you.
Besides, it'll be smooth sailing
if we hire someone new!
That's it!
Masakichi @masakichi_1111
I'm thinking about starting a new channel.
Looking for anyone who wants to join!!
If you're interested, please send me a message.
#Masakichi #RecruitingNewMembers #NewTube
Here we go!
Time for a casting call!
Banpai Manor
Go ahead...
Make a meal of me
I can't think straight,
and it's driving me wild!
I'm at my limit!
Time to dig in!
Hot!
I'm on fire!
My hand! My hand!
Hot, hot, hot!
Pipe down, will you?
Do you know what time it is?
Live-sama!
Hey, Ichiko.
You almost turned me to ashes.
Don't open the curtains in a vampire's room.
I forgot to close them after cleaning.
More importantly, I'm happy
to see you're finally awake!
Huh?
I'm going back to sleep, though.
Back to my dream to...
You can't be serious!
I've been worried sick these last twenty years!
Did you say twenty years?
I sure did!
It was a royal pain watching
you sleep this whole time!
If I was sleeping for twenty years,
why'd I get interrupted at the best part?
I will say, you really are
my savior, Live-sama!
Huh? Your savior?
Thud!
Take a look at this!
What're all these?
Pay us back
Collection Letter
Pay  back   what  you  owe
Collation letters.
Collection letters.
I've been working my butt off to look after
Banpai Manor these past twenty years.
But the debt just keeps piling up.
Wait, debt? How?
I started trading stocks.
What? You of all people?
Yes!
I invested all over. Futures trading.
I'm staying ahead of the game!
How can someone who can't read
the word "collection" even trade stocks?
I consulted videos from
stock market experts, you know.
They promised I'd rake in the cash
if I did as they said!
Save up ¥10 million
Investing in Stocks
Tips & Tricks
Stocks
Guaranteed not to fail
The Hype-Sis Scandal
in 3 Minutes!!
Videos?
What's this rectangular slab?
It's called a smartphone.
Hold it right there!
The Hype-Sis Scandal
in 3 Minutes!!
Now this is a wild turn of events!
Rental Space
Masakichi Channel
New Member Auditions
Conference Room B
Thank you for your application.
Masakichi New Channel
Member Interviews
Um...
Yay.
Without further ado...
I snuck into an interview for the disgraced
NewTuber Masakichi's new member auditions.
No lies. I'm really here.
Um...
But man, right before me
is Little Miss Canceled herself!
Um, if you were to join as a member...
Oh, I'm not here to join.
Hey, do you mind if I upload
this video to my channel?
Please leave.
What a relief.
He looks a lot more serious!
Um, if you were to join as a member...
Ah, could I ask you a question first?
Huh? Yeah, sure.
Go ahead.
Do you have anything you'd like to say
to the two current members of Hype-Sis?
Huh?
Well, um... Not really.
You must be angry, having to leave by yourself.
They were bad-mouthing you
on yesterday's stream, as well.
Those jerks...
I mean, in the first place...
Is that thing recording?
Please leave.
My little brother is very ill,
and he's a fan of yours.
Oh, really?
Then why don't we...
You Got Pranked
Just kidding!
Get out!
Please! Let me taste that punch of yours!
We're here to celebrate
our third day as a couple!
Break up.
Find happiness with these products!
Take that!
A mascot suit?!
How?!
Where am I?
Hell.
All right, time to come back to life!
Guess it makes sense.
The only people who would come are trolls.
Miyama VS Hirata  @miyamavshirata
Looks like all she cares about is getting hits.
So desperate for attention, it makes me sick.
HSHS  @HSHSHSHS
no one's gonna join your
awful despotic channel lmao
runrunboy  @runrunboy
I'm a veteran Hype-Sis fan, and the videos
Masakichi planned have way less hits.
Now I realize her personality must be
why she can't come up with any decent ideas.
Hot Chili Pepper  @hotchilipepper
The nerve to punch someone, never apologize,
and now recruit new members. Zero common sense.
shuu  @shuu27
maybe i should go laugh at her.
and expose her as a disgrace.
1234go  @1234go
Why don't you start by saying sorry?
Maybe I'll go get a drink.
You have a message from Live.
We've been brought together by fate.
My heart races thinking about you...
Man, this is amazing! And convenient!
You can do anything on this thing!
Live-sama, you drank all of our blood rations?!
Sorry, sorry.
I haven't had blood in twenty years!
Now then, did she reply to my DM?
Nothing yet?!
I haven't had a drop to drink today...
Can you believe it, though?!
The girl from my dream exists in real life!
So her name's Masakichi-chan!
The Hype-Sis Scandal in 3 Minutes!!
Wait, hold on!
Was it a prophetic dream?
Did I have that power?
I'm totally unstoppable!
Live-sama is lost in her thoughts.
She must be coming up
with a way to pay off my debts!
I love you, Live-sama!
Ah, I can't wait to suck
Masakichi-chan's blood!
Just slurp it all up!
She's racking her brains, all for my sake!
Could Live-sama be in love with me?
Hey! Give us our money!
Fear not!
I won't let anyone
disturb Live-sama's thoughts!
I can't just go in for a big bite, right?
We need to get to know each other first...
But can I really hold myself back?
I guess we should start with greetings.
Oh, but we've already met in my dream.
Wait a second!
Could it be that I've shown up
in her dreams, too?!
Ugh!
Just thinking about it is too much!
Huh?
Ichiko?
Hey, are you okay?
Damn it, where'd she go?
I can't cause trouble for Live-sama!
Die.
What the hell? Huh?
I'm so low on blood,
I can't even lift a finger...
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
Are you okay?
Wahhh
You're going to burn me alive and
turn me into smoked meat, aren't you?!
Please don't!
I pair well with anything except garlic chips!
Who the hell are you?!
Ah, Live-sama...
You came to save me.
Miss! Miss!
Excuse me...
Another shochu on the rocks!
We're about to close for the night.
I don't want to lose to them.
You know, I was the one who suggested
the three of us start making videos!
Huh, what?
Look, we're closing—
So why?
Why?!
Why am I the one getting kicked out?!
Ma'am, we're closing—
I heard you the first time!
Also, the auditions today...
Hey.
You're Masakichi-san from
Hyped-Up Sisters, aren't you?
Don't start causing trouble
for people in real life, too.
Ah, yes.
Sorry...
What the hell's her deal?
All anyone does is try and kick me out.
It's people like them
shitposting in my replies.
Drop dead!
Ugh, I'm totally wasted.
But there's no way
I'm going back to that house.
An abandoned hospital...
Haunted spots...
The first video of ours that went viral...
Hey, there!
Today on Hype-Sis...
We're visiting an abandoned hospital!
Visiting an abandoned hospital!!
That's right! We received
special permission for today
to shoot a video at the abandoned
hospital that's said to be haunted!
Thank you for giving us permission!!
Okay, let's go ahead and take a look!
Masakichi Channel!
I'm here at an abandoned hospital!
...tal!
S-So empty...
There, there.
I just need to get a viral video.
C'mon! I can take on any ghosts or whatever!
It's too dark to see very well.
Now then, where's our ghost—
So cold! Where'd that water come from?!
Gross. Really?
Ow!
What the hell am I doing?
Wait, I see something here.
What? A real ghost?
Look, here.
Huh? Let me see.
Nah, that's just a reflection.
C'mon, let's hurry up and go further in!
Yeah, sure.
I swear.
Can't you act a little more
scared for the camera?
Sorry, sorry.
I'm all alone.
I just wanted to have fun and get
lots of people to watch our videos.
That's the reason I worked so hard.
But it's all gone now.
I can't believe Ichiko let
our blood supply run out.
Of course I'm the one who drank it.
Why isn't there any blood in this hospital?
Wait, why's this place so empty?
And dark, to boot.
Must have closed down.
Man, really?!
This place was packed twenty years ago!
Wh-What?
I just caught a whiff of
some really tasty blood!
Oh, man, no way! Really?!
What's going on?
My entire body's about to go crazy.
Found you.
H-Hey, you're Masakichi-san, right?
Nice to meet you.
I'm... Live.
U-Um, could it be that you've been
dreaming about me, too?
What kind of question is that?!
Have you?!
I need...
I need to say something...
D-Do you mind if I use the bathroom?
Ugh, I love your voice, too!
I can't do it!
I'm about to lose all control!
The bathroom...
I... want you!
Nope, sorry!
What's with her?
None of this makes any sense!
Wait up!
First, let's get to know each other!
She's gonna get me!
Hey!
Don't change directions so quickly!
Something's obviously weird about her!
Is she...
Could she be...
Let me suck your blood!
She's got to be a vampire!
Stay back!
Huh? Spaciu—
It's a cross!
If you come any closer...
That's dangerous.
Go away!
Once you're gone, I'll come down!
Okay, okay!
Just one bite!
You can spare just one, right?
Don't say it like you're bumming a cig!
What in the world are you?!
It's dangerous, so come down.
Go away!
Not happening.
I know!
Look at this!
You know, I saw this video...
The Hype-Sis Scandal in 3 Minutes!!
This is you, right?
Besides, it'll be smooth sailing
if we hire someone new!
Yay.
Don't start causing trouble
for people in real life, too.
Not like anyone wants to see
a violent bitch like you.
Shut up!
I don't care about any of that anymore!
No one...
No one... needs me anymore!
That's why...
I need you.
I've hit the jackpot with your blood.
It's legit one of a kind.
It's over.
I'm dead.
That's fine.
I'm so tired, anyway.
What?
I told you it was dangerous.
Gotcha!
Well?
Being caught's not so bad, huh?
Wow, I'm flying!
This is out of this world!
There!
Baaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaarrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrffffffffffffffffffffffffffffffffffffff
A-Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Man, that was a blast!
Hey!
You want my blood, right?
How about this?
Can you help me out?
What?
Star in my videos.
If you do, I can make videos
that no one's seen before!
I bet I could reach a million
subscribers in no time!
That's why...
That's why!
I want you to join me!
In exchange, once we hit a million subs...
Go ahead. Make a meal of me.
Live
Sent you a sticker
Goodnight
I'm Masaki!
Live here!
Here we go!
We'll make a vampire channel like none other!
Let's go!
We'll show those two jerks what's what!
Jerk #1
Jerk #2
By the way, what's a "channel"?
For real?
For real.
For real, huh?
Next time: "Starting a Channel!
Good Morning from the Dead of Night!"
Starting a Channel!
Good Morning from the Dead of Night!
Make sure you hit that like and subscribe!